Finding Aid for the Fred Russell Initial Sort
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Fred Russell Initial Sort
multiple
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0376
49.59 linear_feet
- Associations
  - FCA- Fellowship of Christian Athletes 1963 Hylake (Box 1)
  - FWA- Football Writers Association, 1965 (Box 1)
  - FWAA- Football Writers Association of America 1966 Executive Committee (Box 1)
  - NCAA- Council, 1951 (Box 1)
  - NCAA-AAU- National Collegiate Athletic Association- Amateur Athletic Union, 1965 (Box 1)
  - NCAA, 1984 (Box 1)
  - NFSHSAA- National Federation of State Fligh School Athletic Associations (Box 1)
  - NSSA- National Sportscasters and Sportswriters Association (Box 1)
  - NTWA- National Turf Writers Association 35th, 36th, and 37th Annual Dinner Programs (Box 1)
  - SEC- South Eastern Conference- 1983 History (Box 1)
  - SEC- South Eastern Conference- (Box 1)
  - SEC- Tigert, Dr. John J. (Box 1)
  - TRA- Thoroughbred Racing Association- Grantland Rice Scholarship (Box 1)
  - TRA- Thoroughbred Racing Association- Grantland Rice Scholarship (Box 1)
  - TRA- Thoroughbred Racing Association- Grantland Rice Scholarship (Box 1)
  - TRA- Thoroughbred Racing Association- Grantland Rice Scholarship (Box 1)
  - TRA- Thoroughbred Racing Association- Grantland Rice Scholarship (Box 1)
  - TRA- Thoroughbred Racing Association- Grantland Rice Scholarship, 1954 (Box 1)
  - TRA- Thoroughbred Racing Association- Grantland Rice Scholarship, 1957 (Box 1)
  - TRA- Thoroughbred Racing Association- Grantland Rice Scholarship, 1968 (Box 1)
  - TRA- Thoroughbred Racing Association- Grantland Rice Scholarship, 1969 (Box 1)
  - TRA- Thoroughbred Racing Association- Grantland Rice Scholarship, 1972 (Box 1)
  - TRA- Thoroughbred Racing Association- Grantland Rice Scholarship, 1976 (Box 1)
  - TRA- Thoroughbred Racing Association- Grantland Rice Scholarship, 1983 (Box 1)
  - TRA- Thoroughbred Racing Association- Grantland Rice Scholarship, 1986 (Box 1)
  - TRA- Thoroughbred Racing Association- Grantland Rice Scholarship, Celebration, May 1986 (Box 1)
  - TRA- Thoroughbred Racing Association- Fred Russell- Grantland Rice Scholarship (Box 1)
  - TRA- Thoroughbred Racing Association- Fred Russell- Grantland Rice Scholarship (Box 1)
  - TRA- Thoroughbred Racing Association- Fred Russell- Grantland Rice Scholarship (Box 1)
  - TRA- Thoroughbred Racing Association- Fred Russell- Grantland Rice Scholarship (Box 1)
  - TRA- Thoroughbred Racing Association- Fred Russell- Grantland Rice Scholarship (Box 1)
  - TRA- Thoroughbred Racing Association- Fred Russell- Grantland Rice Scholarship (Box 1)
  - TRA- Thoroughbred Racing Association- Fred Russell- Grantland Rice Scholarship (Box 1)
  - TRA- Thoroughbred Racing Association- Fred Russell- Grantland Rice Scholarship (Box 1)
  - TRA- Thoroughbred Racing Association- Fred Russell- Grantland Rice Scholarship (Box 1)
  - TRA- Thoroughbred Racing Association- Fred Russell- Grantland Rice Scholarship (Box 1)
  - TRA- Thoroughbred Racing Association- Fred Russell- Grantland Rice Scholarship (Box 1)
  - TRA- Thoroughbred Racing Association- Fred Russell- Grantland Rice Scholarship (Box 1)
  - TRA- Thoroughbred Racing Association- Fred Russell- Grantland Rice Scholarship Joshua R. Schwartz Application (Box 1)
  - TRA- Thoroughbred Racing Association- Directory and Record Book, 1992, 1994, 1995, 1996, 1997 (Box 1)
- Athletes, Coaches, and Officials
  - Baseball- Aaron, Hank 714/715 (Box 2)
  - Baseball- Alexander, Grover Cleveland (Box 2)
  - Baseball- Appling, Luke (Box 2)
  - Baseball- Cobb, Ty (Tyrus) (Box 2)
  - Baseball- DiMaggio, Joe (Box 2)
  - Baseball- Douglas, Phil (Box 2)
  - Baseball- Feller, Bob (Box 2)
  - Baseball- Gehrig, Lou (Box 2)
  - Baseball- Grove, Lefty (Box 2)
  - Baseball- Hornsby, Rogers (Box 2)
  - Baseball- Jackson, Joe (Box 2)
  - Baseball- Johnson, Walter (Box 2)
  - Baseball- Larsen, Don No-Hitter, Oct. 1950 (Box 2)
  - Baseball- Mantle, Mickey (Box 2)
  - Baseball- Musial, Stan (Box 2)
  - Baseball- Ott, Mel (Box 2)
  - Baseball- Paige, Satchel (Box 2)
  - Baseball- Richards, Paul (Box 2)
  - Baseball- Rose, Pete (Box 2)
  - Baseball- Ruth, George Herman (Babe) (Box 2)
  - Baseball- Thomson, Bobby Homer, Oct.3, 1951 (Box 2)
  - Baseball- Vander Meer, Johnny (Box 2)
  - Baseball- Wagner, Honus (Box 2)
  - Baseball- Waner, Paul (Box 2)
  - Baseball- Williams, Ted (Box 3)
  - Baseball- Young, Cy (Box 3)
  - Baseball- Pitches (Box 3)
  - Baseball- Catchers (Box 3)
  - Baseball- First Basemen (Box 3)
  - Baseball- Second Basemen (Box 3)
  - Baseball- Third Basemen (Box 3)
  - Baseball- Shortstops (Box 3)
  - Baseball- Outfielders (Box 3)
  - Baseball- Umpires (Box 3)
  - Baseball- Bush, Donie (Box 3)
  - Baseball- Chandler, A.B. (Happy) (Box 3)
  - Baseball-Dressen, Charlie (Box 3)
  - Baseball- Dugan, Ken Lipscomb Dinner (Box 3)
  - Baseball- Engel, Joe (Box 3)
  - Baseball- Klem, Bill (Box 3)
  - Baseball- Landis, K. M. (Judge) (Box 3)
  - Baseball- McGaw, John J. (Box 3)
  - Baseball- MacPhail, Larry (Box 3)
  - Baseball- Rickey, Branch (Box 3)
  - Basketball- Newton, C.M. (Box 3)
  - Basketball- Rupp, Adolph F. (Box 3)
  - Basketball- Vamell, Lon (Box 3)
  - Boxing- Ali, Muhammad (Cassius Clay) (Box 3)
  - Boxing- Dempsey, Jack (Box 3)
  - Boxing- Jacobs, Mike (Box 3)
  - Boxing- Louis, Joe (Box 3)
  - Boxing- Marciano, Rocky (Box 3)
  - Football- Brennan, Terry (Box 4)
  - Football- Brennan, Terry (Letters on Story) (Box 4)
  - Football- Brennan, Terry Materials (Box 4)
  - Football- Brown, Paul (Box 4)
  - Football- Broyles, Frank (Box 4)
  - Football- Broyles, Frank (Box 4)
  - Football- Broyles, Frank (Box 4)
  - Football- Butts, Wally (Box 4)
  - Football- Butts, Wally Trial (Box 4)
  - Football- Conner, Mike (Commissioner) (Box 4)
  - Football- Dietzel, Paul (Box 4)
  - Football- Dodd, Robert (Box 4)
  - Football- Dodd, Robert (Box 4)
  - Football- Elias, Bill (Box 4)
  - Football- Gillman, Sid (Box 4)
  - Football- Grange, Red (Box 4)
  - Football- Heard, T.P. Red (Box 4)
  - Football- Hickman, Herman (Box 4)
  - Football- Homung, Paul (Box 4)
  - Football- Knox, Ronnie (Box 4)
  - Football- Leahy, Frank (Box 4)
  - Football- Leahy, Frank Resignation (Box 4)
  - Football- Lombardi, Vince (Box 4)
  - Football- MacLeod, Robert F. (Box 4)
  - Football- Majors, Shirley (Box 4)
  - Football- Nelson, Lindsey (Box 4)
  - Football- Neyland, General Robert Dinner (Box 4)
  - Football- Neyland, General Robert Touchdown Engineer (Box 4)
  - Football- Neyland, General Robert Tennessee (Box 4)
  - Football- Neyland, General Robert (Box 4)
  - Football- Riegels, Roy (Box 4)
  - Football- Rockne, Knute (Box 4)
  - Football- Rote, Kyle (Box 4)
  - Football- Sanders, Red UCLA (Box 5)
  - Football- Sanders, Red UCLA and Florida (Box 5)
  - Football- Shula, Don (Box 5)
  - Football- Thorpe, Jim (Box 5)
  - Football- Trippi, Charley (Box 5)
  - Football- Trippi, Charley (Box 5)
  - Football- Warner, Pop (Box 5)
  - Football- Wyatt, Bowden (Box 5)
  - Football- Wyatt, Bowden (Box 5)
  - Football- Yost, Fielding (Box 5)
  - Football- Zuppke, Robert (Box 5)
  - Football-Bryant, Rockne, Lombardi (Box 5)
  - Football- Four Horsemen (Box 5)
  - Football- Living Player/Coaches 1991 (for election into the Hall of Fame) (Box 5)
  - Football- Greatest Players (Box 5)
  - Football- Great Coaches, Players (Box 5)
  - Golf- Didrickson (Babe Didrickson Zaharias) (Box 5)
  - Golf- Hogan, Ben (Box 5)
  - Golf- Jones, Bobby (Box 5)
  - Golf- Stranahan, Frank (Box 5)
  - Horse Racing- Arcaro, Eddie (Box 5)
  - Horse Racing- Bradley, E.R. (Box 5)
  - Horse Racing- Cauthen, Steve (Box 5)
  - Softball- Hunter, John (Box 5)
  - Tennis- Ashe, Arthur (Box 5)
  - Tennis- Richardson, Ham (Box 5)
  - Tennis- Tilden, Bill (Box 5)
  - Track and Field- Bannister, Roger (Box 5)
  - Wrestling- Londos, Jim (Box 5)
- Awards
  - APSE- Associated Press Sports Editors, Red Smith Award (Box 6)
  - Columbia University- Graduate School of Journalism, Grantland Rice Scholarship (Box 6)
  - DAC- Downtown Athletic Club, Heisman Trophy, 1970, 1972 (Box 6)
  - DAC- Downtown Athletic Club, Heisman Trophy, 1997 (Box 6)
  - DAC- Downtown Athletic Club, Heisman Trophy Mise. Materials (Box 6)
  - DAC- Downtown Athletic Club, DAC Journal, Dec. 1970, Dec. 1971, and Dec. 1972 (Box 6)
  - DAC- Downtown Athletic Club, DAC Journal, Dec. 1973 and Dec. 1975 (Box 6)
  - DAC- Downtown Athletic Club, Heisman Trophy Award Program, 1987, 1993, and 1994 (Box 6)
  - DAC- Downtown Athletic Club, Heisman Trophy Award Program, 1996, and 1997 (Box 6)
  - FWAA- Football Writers Association of America- Outland Trophy (Box 6)
  - Nashville Banner- Banquet of Champions, 1950’s (Box 6)
  - Nashville Banner- Banquet of Champions, 1960 (Box 6)
  - Nashville Banner- Banquet of Champions, 1962 (Box 6)
  - NBHF- National Baseball Hall of Fame and Museum (Box 6)
  - NBHF- National Baseball Hall of Fame and Museum, Cooperstown (Box 6)
  - NBHF- National Baseball Hall of Fame and Museum, Mise. (Box 6)
  - NCAA- National Collegiate Athletic Association, 1982 (Box 6)
  - NCAA- National Collegiate Athletic Association, 1983 San Diego (Box 6)
  - NCAA- National Collegiate Athletic Association, 1984-1985 Top Ten (Box 6)
  - NCAA- National Collegiate Athletic Association, 1985 Convention (Box 6)
  - NCAA- National Collegiate Athletic Association, 1986 Convention, New Orleans (Box 6)
  - NCAA- National Collegiate Athletic Association, 1987 (Box 6)
  - NCAA- National Collegiate Athletic Association, Honors Luncheon, 1978, 1982, 1983 (Box 6)
  - NCAA- National Collegiate Athletic Association, Honors Luncheon, 1985, 1987, 1988 and 1989 (Box 6)
  - NCAA- National Collegiate Athletic Association, Theodore Roosevelt Award 1967 Houston (Box 6)
  - NCAA- National Collegiate Athletic Association, Controversy, 1988 (Box 6)
  - NCAA- National Collegiate Athletic Association, Mise. (Box 6)
  - National Headliners Club (Box 6)
  - NSSA- National Sportscasters and Sportswriters Awards, 1976 and 1977 Sportswriters Hall of Fame Salisbury, North Carolina (Box 6)
  - NSSA- Awards (Box 6)
  - Sigma Delta Chi- Award Nomination Form (Box 6)
  - South Carolina Athletic Hall of Fame- Columbia South Carolina (Box 6)
  - Sport Magazine- Top Performers of the Year Banquet, 1950 (Box 6)
  - Sport Magazine- Top Performers of the Year Banquet, 1950 (Box 6)
  - Sportmenship Brotherhood- Rice Award (Box 6)
  - Sportmenship Brotherhood- Rice Award (Box 6)
  - Sportmenship Brotherhood- Rice Award (Box 6)
  - Sportmenship Brotherhood- Rice Award (Box 6)
  - Sportmenship Brotherhood- Rice Award (Box 6)
  - Tennessee Newspaper Hall of Fame (Box 6)
  - Tennessee Sports Hall of Fame, 1981 (Box 6)
  - Tennessee Sports Hall of Fame, 1994 (Box 6)
  - Touchdown Club of Columbus- 1984 Awards Dinner, Columbus, Ohio (Box 6)
- Awards/ National Football Foundation and Hall of Fame
  - NFFHF- Past Dinners, 1964, 1966, 1967 and 1968 (Box 7)
  - NFFHF, 1968 (Box 7)
  - NFFHF, 1969 (Box 7)
  - NFFHF, 1969 Banquet (Box 7)
  - NFFHF, 1969 Honors Court (Box 7)
  - NFFHF, 1971 Dinner (Box 7)
  - NFFHF, 1972 (Box 7)
  - NFFHF, 1972 Dinner (Box 7)
  - NFFHF, 1973 Dinner (Box 7)
  - NFFHF, 1974 (Box 7)
  - NFFHF, 1974 Dinner (Box 7)
  - NFFHF, 1974 Honors Court (Box 7)
  - NFFHF, 1975 Dinner (Box 7)
  - NFFHF, 1976 (Box 7)
  - NFFHF, 1976 (Box 7)
  - NFFHF, 1976 (Box 7)
  - NFFHF, 1976 Honors Court (Box 7)
  - NFFHF, 1977 Dinner (Box 7)
  - NFFHF, 1977 Honors Court (Box 7)
  - NFFHF, 1978 (Box 7)
  - NFFHF, 1978 Dinner (Box 7)
  - NFFHF, 1978 Honors Court (Box 7)
  - NFFHF, 1978 Kings Island (Box 7)
  - NFFHF, 1979 (Box 7)
  - NFFHF, 1979 Dinner (Box 7)
  - NFFHF, 1979 Kings Island (Box 7)
  - NFFHF, 1980 (Box 7)
  - NFFHF, 1980 Honors Court (Box 7)
  - NFFHF, 1981 (Box 7)
  - NFFHF, 1981 (Box 7)
  - NFFHF, 1981 Honors Court (Box 7)
  - NFFHF, 1982 (Box 7)
  - NFFHF, 1982 Dinner (Box 7)
  - NFFHF, 1982 Honors Court (Box 7)
  - NFFHF, 1984 Dinner (Box 8)
  - NFFHF, 1984 Honors Court (Box 8)
  - NFFHF, 1985 (Box 8)
  - NFFHF, 1986 Honors Court (Box 8)
  - NFFHF, 1987 Honors Court (Box 8)
  - NFFHF, 1988 Dinner (Box 8)
  - NFFHF, 1989 Honors Court (Box 8)
  - NFFHF, 1990 Honors Court (Box 8)
  - NFFHF, 1991 (Box 8)
  - NFFHF, 1995 (Box 8)
  - NFFHF, 1996 (Box 8)
  - NFFHF, 1997 (Box 8)
  - NFFHF Program- Hall of Fame Bowl, 1977 (Box 8)
  - NFFHF Program- 21st Annual Awards Dinner (Box 8)
  - NFFHF Program- 22nd Annual Awards Dinner (Box 8)
  - NFFHF Program- 24th Annual Awards Dinner (Box 8)
  - NFFHF Program- 24th Annual Awards Dinner, Seating List (Box 8)
  - NFFHF Program- 2711’ Annual Awards Dinner (Box 8)
  - NFFHF Program- 29lh Annual Awards Dinner (Box 8)
  - NFFHF Program- 31st Annual Awards Dinner (Box 8)
  - NFFFIF Program- 33rd Annual Awards Dinner (Box 8)
  - NFFHF Program- 34th Annual Awards Dinner (Box 8)
  - NFFHF Program- 36th Annual Awards Dinner (Box 8)
  - NFFHF Program- 37th Annual Awards Dinner (Box 8)
  - NFFHF- Kings Island (Box 8)
  - NFFHF- Kings Island, 1980 (Box 8)
  - NFFHF- Kings Island, 1982 (Box 8)
  - NFFHF- McDowell, Jimmie (Box 8)
  - NFFHF- Misc. (Box 8)
  - NFFHF- Misc. (Box 8)
  - NFFHF- Middle Tennessee Chapter, 1979 Dinner (Box 8)
  - NFFHF- Middle Tennessee Chapter, 1980 Dinner (Box 8)
  - NFFHF- Middle Tennessee Chapter, 1982 Dinner (Box 8)
  - NFFHF- Middle Tennessee Chapter, 1983 Dinner (Box 8)
  - NFFHF- Middle Tennessee Chapter, 1986 Dinner (Box 8)
  - NFFHF- Middle Tennessee Chapter, 1987 Dinner (Box 8)
  - NFFHF- Middle Tennessee Chapter, 1988-1989 Dinner (Box 8)
  - NFFHF- Middle Tennessee Chapter, 1990 Dinner (Box 8)
  - NFFHF- Middle Tennessee Chapter, 1991 and 1993 Dinner (Box 8)
  - NFFHF- Middle Tennessee Chapter, 1994, 1995, 1996 and 1997 Dinner (Box 8)
- Baseball
  - Baseball- Ball Signs (Box 9)
  - Baseball- Base Stealing (Box 9)
  - Baseball- Comedians (Box 9)
  - Baseball- Commissionership 1951 Miami Beach (Box 9)
  - Baseball- Development of Rookies (Box 9)
  - Baseball- Executives Conference “Trautman U.” 1949 (Box 9)
  - Baseball- Fixes Black Sox (Box 9)
  - Baseball- Freak Plays (Box 9)
  - Baseball- Hitting (Box 9)
  - Baseball- Humor (Box 9)
  - Baseball-Junior (Box 9)
  - Baseball- Kitty League (Box 9)
  - Baseball- Negro in Baseball (Box 9)
  - Baseball- Nightball (Box 9)
  - Baseball- No Hit Games (Box 9)
  - Baseball- Odd Characters (Box 9)
  - Baseball- Oddities (Box 9)
  - Baseball- Opening (Box 9)
  - Baseball- Pinch Hitting (Box 9)
  - Baseball- Pitching (Box 9)
  - Baseball- Poems (Box 9)
  - Baseball- Reserve Clause (Gardella) (Box 9)
  - Baseball- Official Scoring (Box 9)
  - Baseball- Scouts (Box 9)
  - Baseball- Scouts and Scouting (Box 9)
  - Baseball- Spring Training, 1983 (Box 9)
  - Baseball- Spring Training (Box 9)
  - Baseball- Songs and Verse (Box 9)
  - Baseball- Southern League Presidency, 1947 (Box 9)
  - Baseball- Strike, 1981 (Box 9)
  - Baseball- Tennessee Native in Major Leagues (Box 9)
  - Baseball- Triple Plays (Box 9)
  - Teams (Box 10)
  - Baseball- Braves (Box 10)
  - Baseball- Mets, 1969 (Box 10)
  - Baseball- Reds, 1979 (Box 10)
  - Baseball- Sounds (Box 10)
  - Baseball- Sounds, 1979 (Box 10)
  - Baseball- West Point Generals (Box 10)
  - Baseball- Yankees (Box 10)
  - Subject Files (Box 10)
  - Baseball- Bats (Box 10)
  - Baseball- Editorials (Box 10)
  - Baseball- Federal League of, 1914-1915 (Box 10)
  - Baseball- Florida (Box 10)
  - Baseball- History (Box 10)
  - Baseball- Major League Baseball (Box 10)
  - Baseball- Managing, Technical, Playing the Game (Box 10)
  - Baseball- Misc. (Box 10)
  - Baseball- Misc. (Box 10)
  - Baseball- National League, 100 Years of (Box 10)
  - Baseball- National League, 1996 Green Book (Box 10)
  - Baseball- Promotion (Box 10)
  - Baseball- Sporting News Diamond Jubilee (Baseball History) (Box 10)
  - Baseball- Trivia (Box 10)
  - Baseball- Miscellaneous (Box 10)
- Football
  - Football- Games GA Tech 222, Cumberland 0 (Box 11)
  - Football- Games Centre College 1921 Charlie Moran (Box 11)
  - Football- Games Tennessee- Florida, 1928 (Box 11)
  - Football- Games Notre Dame- Ohio State, 1935 (Box 11)
  - Football- Games Notre Dame- Army, 1946/1947 (Box 11)
  - Football- Games University of Houston-, Tulsa 1968 (Box 11)
  - Football- Games Famous Southern Games (Box 11)
  - Football- Games Memorable Games (Box 11)
  - Football- Games Five All-Time Games, 1969 (Box 11)
  - Football- 100 Years of College Football, 1969 (Box 11)
  - Football- All Time Teams (Box 11)
  - Football- All America Football Teams History (Box 11)
  - Football- All American - Colliers, 1941-1945 (Box 11)
  - Football- All American - Grantland Rice, 1947 (Box 11)
  - Football- All Americans in Later Life (Box 11)
  - Football- All Americans -Crazy (Box 11)
  - Football- All America Teams (Box 11)
  - Football- All SEC 1950- 1975 (Birmingham Quarterback Club Teams) (Box 11)
  - Football- Top 20 Lists, Yearly (Box 11)
  - Football- Football Polls, 1970 (Box 11)
  - Football- AP-UPI Polls -Athlon (Box 11)
  - Football- Bowl Outline (Box 11)
  - Football- Gator Bowl, 1955 (Box 11)
  - Football- Orange Bowl 1947 Tennessee- Rice (Box 11)
  - Football- Orange Bowl, 1958 (Box 11)
  - Football- Rose Bowl (Box 11)
  - Football- Rose Bowl (Reunion of Alabama’s 1925 Team) (Box 11)
  - Football- Rose Bowl, 1939 (Box 11)
  - Football- Rose Bowl 1945 (Box 11)
  - Football- Rose Bowl 1954 UCLA- Michigan State (Box 11)
  - Football- Rose Bowl, 1974 (Box 11)
  - Football- Senior Bowl (Box 11)
  - Football- Georgia Tech (withdrawal from SEC) (Box 12)
  - Football- Mooney Football (Box 12)
  - Football- Notre Dame (Box 12)
  - Football- Princeton (Box 12)
  - Football- Sewanee (Box 12)
  - Football- Sewanee 1899 Ironmen (Box 12)
  - Football- Sewanee, 1966 (Box 12)
  - Football- Vols Football (Box 12)
  - Football- West Point (Box 12)
  - Football- West Point, McWilliams, 1946 (Box 12)
  - Football- West Point Cribbing, 1951 (Box 12)
  - Football- College Football (Box 12)
  - Football- College Football 1996 SEC, Mostly Scholarship (Box 12)
  - Football- History “Football’s Origins: The Rest of the Story” (Box 12)
  - Football- History “History of the Game” (Box 12)
  - Football- History “ The Second Half: From the Lago Mar to Instant Replay” (Box 12)
  - Football- History, 1956 (Box 12)
  - Football- History Misc. (Box 12)
  - Football- History Misc. (Box 12)
  - Football- History Misc. (Box 12)
  - Football- History Petersen’s Publishing Co. (Box 12)
  - Football- History Big Ten vs Pacific Coast (Box 12)
  - Football- History “The True Story of Football” Charleston, WV Gazette (Box 12)
  - Football- Misc. (Box 12)
  - Football- Misc. (Box 12)
  - Football- Misc. GA Bulldogs, Eric Zier, and Jerry Clower (Box 12)
  - Football- Misc. (Box 12)
  - Football- Academic Standards (University of Texas Story) (Box 12)
  - Football- Benefits and Evils of the Game (Box 12)
  - Football- Coaching (Box 12)
  - Football- Coaching School, Herald- Tribune (Box 12)
  - Football- Discontinued College Football (War) (Box 12)
  - Football- Finance-Business (Box 12)
  - Football- Gambling (Box 12)
  - Football- Humor (Box 12)
  - Football- Mental Side (Box 12)
  - Football- Officiating (Box 12)
  - Football- Officiating SEC (Box 12)
  - Football- Plays, Diagrams, Strategies (Playing the Game) (Box 12)
  - Football- Publicity-Promotion (Box 12)
  - Football- Public Relations (Box 12)
  - Football- Records, Famous Plays and Oddities (Box 12)
  - Football- Rules (College) (Box 12)
  - Football- Rules NCAA Football Rules Committee Chronology of 100 Years (1876-1976) (Box 12)
  - Football- Split T-Formation (Box 12)
  - Football- T-Formation (Shaughnessy) (Box 12)
  - Football- T-Formation (Box 12)
  - Football- Scholarships (Box 12)
  - Football- Score Cards, Dope Books, How to See a Game (Box 12)
  - Football- Scouting (Box 12)
  - Football- Sportmanship 1991 Althon (Box 12)
  - Football- Touchdown Club Parties (Box 12)
  - Football- Pro Football (Box 13)
  - Football- Pro Football, 1966 (Box 13)
  - Football- Pro Football Oilers (Box 13)
  - Football- Pro Football Superbowl, 1981 (Box 13)
  - Football- PRO!, Publication of the National Football League, Hall of Fame Edition (Box 13)
- Horse Racing
  - Horse Racing- Horse Racing (Box 14)
  - Horse Racing- Horse Racing (Box 14)
  - Horse Racing- Owners, Trainers, and Jockeys (Box 14)
  - Horse Racing- Arabians (Box 14)
  - Horse Racing- Belle Meade -Tennessee Horses (Box 14)
  - Horse Racing- Betting (Box 14)
  - Horse Racing- Breeding (Box 14)
  - Horse Racing- Chart Calling (Box 14)
  - Horse Racing- Dortch Stud Books- Correspondence (Box 14)
  - Horse Racing- Grassland (Box 14)
  - Horse Racing- Handicapping (Box 14)
  - Horse Racing- Harness Racing-Trotting - Goshen (Box 14)
  - Horse Racing- Horse Parks-Hialeah, Pimlico, Oaklawn, Santa Anita, Saratoga, Gulfstream, Sunshine (Box 14)
  - Horse Racing- Humor (Box 14)
  - Horse Racing- Iroquois Steeplechase (Box 14)
  - Horse Racing- Iroquois Steeplechase (Box 14)
  - Horse Racing- Iroquois Steeplechase 1970/1971 (Box 14)
  - Horse Racing- Iroquois Steeplechase, 1990 (Box 14)
  - Horse Racing- Keeneland (Box 14)
  - Horse Racing- Keeneland (Box 14)
  - Horse Racing- Keeneland, 1975 (Box 14)
  - Horse Racing- Keeneland, 1977 (Box 14)
  - Horse Racing- Keeneland, 1978 (Box 15)
  - Horse Racing- Keeneland, 1979 (Box 15)
  - Horse Racing- Keeneland, 1980 (Box 15)
  - Horse Racing- Litkenhous (Box 15)
  - Horse Racing- McCarthy, Clem “Boner” (Box 15)
  - Horse Racing- Milky Way (Box 15)
  - Horse Racing- Naming Horses (Box 15)
  - Horse Racing- Oaklawn Park (How to Win at the ,..) (Box 15)
  - Horse Racing- Oaklawn Park Media Guide, 1991 (Box 15)
  - Horse Racing- Oaklawn Park (Box 15)
  - Horse Racing- Story Subjects (Box 15)
  - Horse Racing- Wyatt Hall Farm, 1967 (Box 15)
  - Horse Racing- Kentucky Derby, 1971 (Box 15)
  - Horse Racing- Kentucky Derby, 1972 (Box 15)
  - Horse Racing- Kentucky Derby, 1972 (Box 15)
  - Horse Racing- Kentucky Derby, 1973 (Box 15)
  - Horse Racing- Kentucky Derby, 1974 (Box 15)
  - Horse Racing- Kentucky Derby, 1975 (Box 15)
  - Horse Racing- Kentucky Derby, 1976 (Box 15)
  - Horse Racing- Kentucky Derby, 1976 (Box 15)
  - Horse Racing- Kentucky Derby, 1977 (Box 15)
  - Horse Racing- Kentucky Derby, 1981 (Box 15)
  - Horse Racing- Kentucky Derby, 1982 (Box 15)
  - Horse Racing- Kentucky Derby, 1984 (Box 15)
  - Horse Racing- Kentucky Derby, 1985 (Box 15)
  - Horse Racing- Kentucky Derby, 1986 (Box 15)
  - Horse Racing- Kentucky Derby, 1988 (Box 15)
  - Horse Racing- Kentucky Derby Media Guide, 1990 (Box 15)
  - Horse Racing- Kentucky Derby Media Guide, 1991 (Box 15)
  - Horse Racing- Kentucky Derby Media Guide, 1992 (Box 15)
  - Horse Racing- Kentucky Derby 1993 Clippings (Box 15)
  - Horse Racing- Kentucky Derby Souvenir Magazine, 1997 (Box 15)
  - Horse Racing- Kentucky Derby 100th Anniversary Book (Box 15)
  - Horse Racing- Kentucky Derby Column Material (Box 15)
  - Horse Racing- Kentucky Derby History (Box 15)
  - Kentucky Derby Misc. (and Story for Churchill Downs News) (Box 16)
  - Kentucky Derby Misc. (Box 16)
  - Kentucky Derby Misc. (Box 16)
  - Horse Racing Misc. Mostly Kentucky Derby (Box 16)
  - Horses- Ace’s Sensation (Box 16)
  - Horses- Cigar (Box 16)
  - Horses- Freddie R. (Box 16)
  - Horses- Kay Russell (Box 16)
  - Horses- Man O’War (Box 16)
  - Horses- Nashville (Box 16)
  - Horses- Saucy (Box 16)
  - Horses- Secretariat (Box 16)
  - Horses- Famous Horses (Box 16)
  - Horses- Greatest Horses -Citation, Phar Lap, Exterminator, Kelso (Box 16)
  - Horses- Swaps-Nashua Match Race, 1955 (Box 16)
- Newspapermen/ Reporters
  - Bishop, Jim (Box 17)
  - Burick, Si (Box 17)
  - Burick, Si (Box 17)
  - Cannon, Jimmy (Box 17)
  - Cohane, Tim (Box 17)
  - Considine, Bob (Box 17)
  - Corum, Bill (Box 17)
  - Cunningham, Bill (Box 17)
  - Danforth, Ed (Box 17)
  - Dawkins, Col. Peter (Box 17)
  - Erwin, Ray (Box 17)